<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cheap Video Games on Deals &amp; Finds</title><link>https://c4duc3u5-py.github.io/c4duc3u5-py.io/tags/cheap-video-games/</link><description>Recent content in Cheap Video Games on Deals &amp; Finds</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 08:46:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://c4duc3u5-py.github.io/c4duc3u5-py.io/tags/cheap-video-games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Video Games Beginner's Guide — Best Deals &amp; Tips 2026</title><link>https://c4duc3u5-py.github.io/c4duc3u5-py.io/video-games-beginners-guide-best-deals-tips-2026/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 08:46:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://c4duc3u5-py.github.io/c4duc3u5-py.io/video-games-beginners-guide-best-deals-tips-2026/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="beginners-guide-to-video-games--everything-you-need-to-know"&gt;Beginner&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Video Games — Everything You Need to Know&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re new to video games, this guide explains what to buy, where to buy, and how to avoid expensive mistakes. You&amp;rsquo;ll learn practical buying tips for hardware and games, how to spot good condition on pre-owned items, and two well-priced listings in the £60–£89 range you can check on eBay UK right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Video games are more than software — they include controllers, VR gear, and tabletop titles that appeal to the same players. This guide covers: how to buy video games online UK, what to inspect when purchasing used gaming hardware, and why a VR knuckle controller or a sealed board game could be smart buys.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Video Games Deals Guide: Spot Best Buys &amp; Save Big</title><link>https://c4duc3u5-py.github.io/c4duc3u5-py.io/video-games-deals-guide-spot-best-buys-save-big/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 11:16:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://c4duc3u5-py.github.io/c4duc3u5-py.io/video-games-deals-guide-spot-best-buys-save-big/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="how-to-spot-a-great-deal-on-video-games-and-vr-gear-and-save-time--money"&gt;How to Spot a Great Deal on Video Games and VR Gear (and Save Time &amp;amp; Money)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A good deal on video games or VR hardware means getting reliable performance, clear seller info, and fair shipping — not just a low price. This guide shows how to evaluate listings on eBay.co.uk, what to inspect in VR controllers and board games, and three vetted listings in the £60–£89 range you can check right now.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Video Games Guide: Best £60–£89 Buys &amp; Deals UK Now</title><link>https://c4duc3u5-py.github.io/c4duc3u5-py.io/video-games-guide-best-6089-buys-deals-uk-now/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 11:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://c4duc3u5-py.github.io/c4duc3u5-py.io/video-games-guide-best-6089-buys-deals-uk-now/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="video-games-what-to-look-for-before-you-buy-and-three-smart-buys-in-the-6089-range"&gt;Video Games: What to look for before you buy (and three smart buys in the £60–£89 range)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to buy video games or related gear in the UK and get good value, know what to check before you click. This guide covers practical checks, care tips and three specific listings on eBay UK in the £60–£89 band — two Valve Index &amp;ldquo;Knuckle&amp;rdquo; controllers and a well-regarded board game — so you can buy video games, controllers and tabletop experiences with confidence.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>